

ABOUT ME

I consider myself a person with the virtue of teamwork and very proactive. I have the ability to help people because of my work experience in the public environment at the service of citizens. In addition, I have great interest to develop in a technology company to gain experience and learn new concepts from my background in web development.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birth date: 07/07/1996 Nationality: Argentina

DNI: 39760338

CONTACT

+54 9 11 34450448

rodriberdomas@gmail.com

Villa Devoto, C.A.B.A.

http://www.linkedin.com/in/rodrig o-berdomas-121a511b2

https://github.com/rodriberdo96

SKILLS

Conflict Resolution.
Service and support.
Solid work ethic.
Javascript
React.js
Express.js

- Great attention to detail.- Node.js- Advanzed english.- Git, Github

- Beginner web developer. - HTML

- Trading.

- Microsoft office.

REFERENCE

Nadia Torres / GTC Ribbon

+ 54 9 11 67803278 nadia@gtcribbon.com

Santiago Delucchi / DGFEP and AGC

+ 54 9 11 32022753 santi.delluchi1987@gmail.com

RODRIGO BERDOMÁS

FRONT-FND WER DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

Greenbriar School (Elementary School)

Chicago, EE.UU. | 2006 - 2007

Northbrook Junior High School

Chicago, EE.UU. | 2007

Social science and Humanities Baccalaureate

Villa Devoto School | 2007 - 2014

Odonthology

Universidad Kennedy | 2017 - 2021

Full Stack Developer

Coderhouse | February 2022 - April 2023

Technical Degree in Software Development

UADE | 2023-Present

EXPERIENCE

Asisstant to Vicepresident

GTC Ribbon | Ocober 2015 - March 2016

- Administrative tasks
- Stock replenishment

Inspector

Dirección General de Fiscalización del Espacio Público (DGFEP) | December 2017 - December 2019

- Inspection and maintenance of ilegal sales in the street on Once, Liniers, Retiro and Avellaneda.
- Attention to the citizen.

Inspector

Agencia Gubernamental de control (AGC) | February 2020 - February 2023

- Inspection and maintenance of ilegal sales in the street on Once, Liniers, Retiro and Avellaneda.
- Attention to the citizen.

Agent

Oficina de Coordinación del Cuerpo de Investigaciones Judiciales | February 2023 - Present

- Inspection tasks for various cases.
- Coordination of comprehensive inspections for the Public Prosecutor's Office.
- Preparation and submission of reports to the relevant prosecutor's offices

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

International Baccalaureate(IB)

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native.English: Fluent.French: basic.